This video will introduce you to automatically generate PBR stickers.
Let's first introduce the concept of PBR stickers.
PBR stickers are also called physical stickers.
They are used to define the interaction of surface properties and simulated light and material in physics-based rendering.
Affect the final visual effect
PBR stickers include physical graphics, simulation graphics, transparent graphics, surface roughness graphics, and metal graphics.
By using them, we can obtain a more realistic and intuitive material performance.
In the previous version, users could not directly generate PBR stickers in Qo.
You need to work back and forth between Qo and Photoshop.
To make the user's workflow more smooth.
Now in our new version,
you can automatically generate PBR stickers in Qo.
We only need to prepare a four-sided continuous texture in advance.
Now select the material in the object window.
Add the texture to the property editor.
Now, in the back of the discovery picture,
there is an automatically generated image.
Click on the button.
Press the button to automatically generate a PBR picture.
You can adjust the intensity of the PBR picture.
In the back of the discovery picture,
the automatic generation button also appears.
Press the button to automatically generate the discovery picture.
In order to make the discovery effect more smooth,
In order to make the simulation effect too natural, we turn on the logic editor,
open the blurring edge,
and adjust the blurring radius.
Let's adjust the simulation picture data again.
Adjust the particle diameter and simulation degree.
Similarly, the transparent picture can also automatically generate PBR stickers.
The surface rough operation picture is also the same operation.
다음에的部分都being able to create still situation appearance.
Ally is also the same operation,
only supported in lubrication enormously due to its standoff with the Mikintree formula.
Then let's generate the PBR sticker of the simulation picture.
This way, the simulation picture load data would also be forced into the simulation picture.
Adjust the data of simulation picture in a DA.
Adjust the rough picture data on the surface.
Now open the physical editor of the metal picture.
Click on the color switch to adjust the black and white gray relationship on the bright side.
Now, the overall effect of the rendering is checked.
The sticker can also automatically generate PBR stickers.
In the property editor,
click the Automated generation button to generate PBR and PBR.
Open the text editor after the PBR is opened,
and select the text editor after the PBR is opened.
Select the color switch,
adjust the background color,
and achieve the desired effect.
Open the blurred edge,
and adjust the blur radius.
Click on the application and turn it off.
Also adjust the data for the change.
Let's take a look at the rendering effect.
In addition to the material and the sticker,
the button, the eye, the line of sight, and the accessory can automatically generate PBR stickers.
The overall image is the same.
If you want a different image,
the color is also different depending on the person
depending on the person who uses it.
Then with the app,
you can see that the color is now the same.
This is the original picture,
which is completely different.
With the app,
the color is only the same.
So this is also the original picture.
The result is also a nice effect.
You can use the optimization of the color.
If you want to make some changes,
here is the communication of colors.
If you want to be able to modify the color that you want,
you can do so.
Click on the object in the top right of the image.
Then the app will be displayed to the left of the information,
and the color will move here.
If you want to change the color,
Thank you.